Guide to the Rice University Smalley Institute for Nanoscale Science and Technology records, 1993-2015 UA 184
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series III: Nanotechnology Initiatives, 2002-2015; 207479
  - Lancer (Lockheed-Martin) Nanotechnology Short Course (1 of 6), 2006 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Lancer (Lockheed-Martin) Nanotechnology Short Course (2 of 6), 2006 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Lancer (Lockheed-Martin) Nanotechnology Short Course (3 of 6), 2006 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Lancer (Lockheed-Martin) Nanotechnology Short Course (4 of 6), 2006 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Lancer (Lockheed-Martin) Nanotechnology Short Course (5 of 6), 2006 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Lancer (Lockheed-Martin) Nanotechnology Short Course (6 of 6), 2006 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Lancer (Lockheed-Martin) Fundamentals & Applications in Nanotechnology Deep Dive, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Lancer (Lockheed-Martin) Fundamentals & Applications in Nanotechnology Short Course (1 of 2), 2008 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Lancer (Lockheed-Martin) Fundamentals & Applications in Nanotechnology Short Course (2 of 2), 2008 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Lancer (Lockheed-Martin) Deep Dive Nanotechnology Course, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - SPRING (Strategic Partnership for Research in Nanotechnology) Consortium, 2002-2004; 207480 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Texas Nanotechnology Initiative, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Series IV: Conferences and Meetings, 2003-2014; 207549
  General
  There are financial records from this series which can be shredded starting in 2015. All financial records are retained for seven years.
  - National Science Foundation Nanoscale & Engineering Conference, December 16-18, 2003; 207601 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Baker Institute: Energy & Nanotechnology Conference, February 2005; 207602 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - UMET Nanotechnology Workshop, September 16, 2005; 207604 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - SAMPE Fall Technology Conference, November 1, 2005; 207605 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Nano Tech Conference Japan, February 21-23, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - APS & US Army Materials Summit, March 12-16, 2006; 207606 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Strategic Partnership for Research in Nanotechnology SPRING IV Conference, February 6-7, 2007; 207543 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - The Best Little Nanoconference in Texas, April 4-5, 2007; 207603 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - CONTACT: Industry/Air Force Nanoscience Research Focus Meeting, October 30-31-2007; 207544 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Nanotechnology Venture Forum, 2007-2008 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Austin Alliance, January 15-16, 2008; 207607 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - SPE Applied Technology Workshop, February 1-8, 2008; 207608 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - AAAS Annual Meeting (cancelled), February 14-18, 2008; 207609 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - 2008 Nano Materials for Defense, April 21-25, 2008; 207610 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - High Polymer Research Group, April 25- May 1, 2008; 207611 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - AEC Workshop, May 19-21, 2008; 207612 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - NSTI Nanotech Clean Technology 2008, June 2-5, 2008; 207613 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Polymer Fibres Conference, July 8-11, 2008; 207614 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Nano Energy Summit, July 21-22, 2008; 207615 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - NIST/Congressional Briefing, July 29-30, 2008; 207617 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - IEEE Nano 2008/Lockheed Martin, August 17-20, 2008; 207618 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - UARC, August 28-29, 2008; 207616 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Airforce Nano-Bio Aerospace Forum, November 5-7, 2008; 207619 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - AFRL, February 3-6, 2009; 207620 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Undergraduate Nanotechnology Conference, February 27-28, 2009; 207621 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Beyong Kyoto: Climate Change, March 3-7, 2009; 207622 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Initiatives in Nanotechnology, April 1-3, 2009; 207623 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Nanotechnology for Defense, April 6-9, 2009; 207624 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Guadalupe Workshop, April 17-21, 2009; 207625 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Mapping US Energy & Climate, April 28-29, 2009; 207626 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - UARC, May 25-27, 2009; 207627 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Yale- Rigaku Symposium, May 29, 2009; 207628 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Formulation of Energy & Climate Policy, June 17-21, 2009; 207629 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - NanoAlberta MOU Signing, September 20-21, 2009; 207630 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Contact Annual Review Meeting, September 26-30, 2009; 207631 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - 24/7 Ignobel Lecture, October 1-2, 2009; 207632 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - SPE 2nd Annual Awards Ceremony, October 13-14, 2009; 207633 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - SAMPE Tech Conference, October 18-21, 2009; 207634 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Tuskegee Science & Technology Open House, October 23-25, 2009; 207635 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Nanoteach Conference 2009, November 2-4, 2009; 207636 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Lancer/Lockheed Martin Steering Committee, January 25-26, 2010; 207637 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Rice Alliance 9th Annual Nanotechnology Venture Forum, February 18, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Nanotube for Space Applications Interchange meeting, March 15-17, 2010; 207638 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Deck & Derrick Club, March 25-27, 2010; 207639 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Materials Research Society Board, April 7-11, 2010; 207640 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - NCURA Region V Spring Meeting, April 25-28, 2010; 207641 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Nanotechnology for Defense, May 3-6, 2010; 207642 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - NASA Johnson Space Center & Rice University Nanotechnology Forum, May 18, 2010; 207507 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - ACS 42nd Central Regional Meeting, June 16-20, 2010; 207643 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Nanotech Clean Technology (NIST), June 21-25, 2010; 207644 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - National Space Missile Materials Symposium, June 26-30, 2010; 207645 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - National Nanotechnology Initiative Planning Workshop (cancelled), July 12-14, 2010; 207646 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Texas Lyceum Conference, August 5-8, 2010; 207647 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Dickinson State University Energy Technology, August 8-10, 2010; 207648 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Materials Research Society, August 19-22, 2010; 207649 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - DC Nano Congressional Reception, September 14-16, 2010; 207650 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - NNI Strategic Planning, September 29-30, 2010; 207651 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - NEES-EFRC Meeting, October 27-28, 2010; 207652 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - NNI Nanotech Innovation Summit, December 8-11, 2010; 207653 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Nanotech in Medicine, December 16, 2010; 207654 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Rice Alliance for Nanotechnology & Entrepreneurship, February 17, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - SAMPE Forecast Forum, February 22-24, 2011; 207655 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - The New Steel (NIST), February 27-March 1, 2011; 207656 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - NCURA, March 22-25, 2011; 207657 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - TECH Connect, June 13-15, 2011; 207658 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - National Aviation Hall of Fame, July 16, 2011; 207659 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Materials Research Society, August 13-16, 2011; 207660 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Nanotechnology for Defense, October 22-28, 2011; 207661 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Materials Research Society, November 28-December 4, 2011; 207662 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Global Forum on the Implications of Regulation on Nanotechnology, January 12, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Nanonuclear Workshop, February 27- March 1, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Transatlantic Science Week- Bridging Partnerships, November 12-16, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Water Management & Nano Energy Summit, November 13-14, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Nanosmat USA, May 19-22, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - NorTex Nano Summit, October 12-15, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 78)
- Series V: Proposals, 1996-2005
  - Department of Energy Basic Energy Sciences, 1996-2002 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Hyperion Catalysis International Inc, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Taraval Associates/ Murphy, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Fullerene Fiber Composites, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Proposal R51480: NASA-JSC/Rice Cooperative Agreement, 1998-2003 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Proposal R36810: Fullerene Nanotube Chemistry, 1999-2003 (Box 8, Folder 6-7)
  - HiPco Inc. Commercialization, 1999-2011 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Proposal R13650: Magnetic/RF Field Assisted Spinning of Carbon SWNF, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Proposal R13573: Fiber Spinning and Liquid Crystalline Behavior of SWNT's, 2000-2003 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Proposal D72555: Synthesis and Assembly of Carbon SWNF's, 2000-2003 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Proposal R82080: Texas ARP/ATP Award, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Nanoscale Science & Engineering Center (NSEC), 2001 (Box 8, Folder 13-14)
  - Proposal R13574: HiPco, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - MRI: Scanning ESCA Microprobe, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Baylor: Imaging of Cellular Processes, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - High Temperature Materials Lab, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Ionwerks, Inc., 2002 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Nanoscale Interdisciplinary Research Team (NIRT), 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - HTML-ORNL, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - NSEC: C Sixty, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - National Nanotechnology Infrastructure Network (NINN): Rice NanoFoundry, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Cloning Single Wall Carbon Nanotubes, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Advanced Characterization System for Single Walled Carbon Nanotubes, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Microwave Nanotube Interactions (DARPA), 2003 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - NREL Carbon Based Hydrogen Storage Center of Excellence, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Development of High-yield Methods for Cutting Single Walled Carbon Nanotubes, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Alliance for Nanohealth, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Synthesis, Purification & Assembly of Carbon Single Walled Carbon Nanotube Fibers, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Single Walled Nanotube Amplifier Demonstration Project, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Mobility Control for CO2 EOR, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Carbon Nanotube (CNT) Infrastructure, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Nano- Bio Aerospace Institute pilot project, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Series VI: Administration, 1995-2014
  - Sub-Series A: Articles
    - Magazine Articles, 1995-2010 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Buckyball Articles, 2002-2010 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Curl Articles, 1996-2008 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - General Science Articles, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Nanotech Articles, 2002-2007 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Nanotube Articles, 2003-2006 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Rice Articles, 9002-2008 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Smalley Articles, 1985-2010 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series B: Events
    - AFOSR/NIST Carbon Workshop, 1990-1993 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Events, 1995-2006 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Bio 97 Meeting, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Carbon Nanotechnology Lab opening, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Lord Sainsbury, UK Minister of Science & Innovation, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - NASA Transformational Technology Lecture, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Nanotube Model, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Congressman Culberson meetings, 2007-2009 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Texas Legislators, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Nano Symphony, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Save the World, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Buckyball Discovery Gala, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Building the Buckyball Sandcastle, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Year of the Nano, 2010-2011 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Houston Technology Center Innovation, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Kroto Lecture, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series C: General administration
    - Grant Funding: PI Smalley, 1992-1999 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Research Quantity Nanotubes, 1993-1998 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Jason Hafner: Mounting of Carbon Nanotubes to Devices, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Dell Butcher Hall, 1995-1998 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Smalley Biography, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Smalley Research Group patent listing, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Video documentation, 1997-2007 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Attwell-Welch PostDoc Fellowship, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Buckyballs, Fullerenes & the Future (Oral History transcript Richard Smalley), 2000 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Report to ACS Committee on Professional Training, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Chemical Hygiene Plan, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - UT Center for Nano and Molecular Science and Technology (CNMst), 2001 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - KTCS Nanotechnology Documentary, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Center for Biological & Environmental Nanotechnology (CBEN), 2003 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Science & Engineering Annual Development Update, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Smalley-Curl Innovation Fund, 2003-2005 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Nano World Headquarters, 2003-2007 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - National Medal of Technology, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Nanotechnology at Rice University, 2004-2005 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Energy Policy, 2005-2010 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - CBEN Annual Report, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Chemical Heritage Foundation, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Smalley Student Society, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Benchmarking Centers & Institutes, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Nanotechnology Patent Proliferation, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Workforce Development, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Rice Institute Directors' Meetings, 2007-2008 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - American Chemical Society- Greater Houston Section, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Chemical Heritage Society, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Institute Planning, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Institute Project management, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Institute Space Inventory, 2008-2010 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - CBEN Annual Report, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Institute Priorities & Tasks, 2009-2013 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - NSTI Promotional Displays, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Speedstorming Center for Controlled Sorption of Energy & Matter, 2009-2011 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Nano Art Project, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Nanotechnology at Rice, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - WTEC: Nanotechnology Long-term Impacts & Research Directions, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Bayer Material Science, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Releases-Promotional, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Security Survey: Space Science 301A, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series D: International Nanotechnology
    - International Nanotechnology, 2008-2009 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Russian Corporation of Nanotechnologies, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Thailand Department of Alternative Energy Development, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Nano-Alberta, 2008-2009 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Alberta Oil Sands, 2010-2011 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Skolkovo, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series E: Nanofans
    - Nanokids, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Nanofans, 2003-2012 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Nanofans: Smalley Institute Fundraising Priorities, 2003-2012 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Development, 2006-2008 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Tuna Fest, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Nanofans Donor Letters, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Nanofans Year of the Nano Development Plans, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Nanofans Donor Lists, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series F: Nanotechnology Companies
    - Nanotechnology Companies in Texas, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Blue Sky Electronics, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Room Temperature Superconductors Inc, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Corporate Contacts, 2008-2013 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Nanotechnology Commercialization in Houston, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - National Corrosion Center, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Rice Alliance Company Directory, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series G: Photographs
    - Negative, Carbon 60 Team, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Photographs, May 2002 (Box 11, Folder 6-7)
    - Slides of Labs (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Photos (DVDs) (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Bucky Tape, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Smalley/Curl Photos, Scans of originals, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Smalley/Curl photos, Scans of originals (Curl Photo Album), 2010 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Smalley/Curl photos, Scans of originals (Smalley Album), 2010 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Series VII: Audio & Video/ Computer disks, 1995-2010
  - CNST Archive - NOVA: Race to Catch a Bucky Ball (DVD), December 19, 1995 (Box 12)
  - CNST Archive 94 - CNN Nobel Minds: Challenges of the 21st Century (DVD), December 15, 1996 (Box 12)
  - CNST Archive: ONR Nanotube Conference Day 1, Center, part 1 (DVD), May 30, 1997 (Box 12)
  - CNST Archive: ONR Nanotube Conference Day 1, Center, part 2 (DVD), May 30, 1997 (Box 12)
  - CNST Archive: ONR Nanotube Conference Day 1, Center, part 3 (DVD), May 30, 1997 (Box 12)
  - CNST Archive: ONR Nanotube Conference Day 1, Center, part 4 (DVD), May 30, 1997 (Box 12)
  - CNST Archive: ONR Nanotube Conference Day 1, Tripod Sony, parts 1-4 (DVD), May 30, 1997 (Box 12)
  - CNST Archive: ONR Nanotube Conference Day 2, Center, part 1 (DVD), May 31, 1997 (Box 12)
  - CNST Archive: ONR Nanotube Conference Day 2, Center, part 2 (DVD), May 31, 1997 (Box 12)
  - CNST Archive: ONR Nanotube Conference Day 2, Center, part 3 (DVD), May 31, 1997 (Box 12)
  - CNST Archive: ONR Nanotube Conference Day 2, Center, part 4 (DVD), May 31, 1997 (Box 12)
  - CNST Archive: ONR Nanotube Conference Day 2, Tripod Sony, parts 1-3 (DVD), May 31, 1997 (Box 12)
  - CNST Archive: ONR Nanotube Conference Day 3, Center, part 1 (DVD), June 1, 1997 (Box 12)
  - CNST Archive: ONR Nanotube Conference Day 3, Center, part 2 (DVD), June 1, 1997 (Box 12)
  - CNST Archive: ONR Nanotube Conference Day 3, Center, part 3 (DVD), June 1, 1997 (Box 12)
  - CNST Archive: ONR Nanotube Conference Day 3, Tripod Sony, parts 1-3 (DVD), June 1, 1997 (Box 12)
  - CNST Archive: Dr. Smalley at UOP (DVD), June 3, 1997 (Box 12)
  - CNST Archive 57: Series of Formal Presentations by Nobel Laureates, Rice University (DVD), November 28, 2000 (Box 12)
  - CNST Archive - Director's Colloquium: Bucky Balls and Nanotubes, Los Alamos National Lab (DVD), December 13, 2000 (Box 12)
  - CNST Archive: National Science Foundation Nanotechnology Symposium with Lecture by Dr. Smalley (DVD), March 19, 2002 (Box 12)
  - CNST Archive: Engineering the Impossible, Powerhouse Productions (DVD), April 26, 2002 (Box 12)
  - CNST Archive: Governor's Council for Science and Technology, Rice University, part 1 (DVD), September 13, 2002 (Box 12)
  - CNST Archive: Governor's Council for Science and Technology, Rice University, part 2 (DVD), September 13, 2002 (Box 12)
  - Celebrating Innovation Dinner: Honoring Richard Smalley, Robert Curl, and CNST, River Oaks Country Club (DVD), November 13, 2002 (Box 12)
  - The 6th Annual Maria Luisa Ferrari Lectureship for Life (featuring Richard E. Smalley) (VHS), 2005 (Box 12)
  - Small is Big at Rice University - Constructing the Guinness World Record Nanotube Model (2 DVDs), April 22, 2005 (Box 12)
  - The Promise of Tomorrow: A compelling story on the lives of two Nobel Laureates, vital pioneers in science and technology, as told by the people who knew them best, A tribute to Jack Kirby and Richard Smalley (2 DVDs), 2006 (Box 12)
  - Richard E. Smalley: Celebrating an Extraordinary Life, Rice University (DVD), March 21, 2006 (Box 12)
  - The American Chemical Society 232nd National Meeting- SWNTs: From Synthesis to Application, "From the Lab to the Fab," In memory of: Dr. Rick Smalley, Presidential Symposium, San Francisco, CA. (DVD), September 10-13, 2006 (Box 12)
    Scope and Contents
    Dr. David Tomanek, Professor of Physics, Michigan State University, "Success Story of Bucky Balls and Nanotubes," n.d. (2 DVDs); Dr. Wade Adams, Director, Smalley Institute for Nanoscience and Technology, "The Vision of Richard E. Smalley: Nanotechnology in Energy, Be a Scientist - Save the World," n.d. (2 DVDs)
  - Alumni College Weekend 2007 - "Hitching a Ride on a Comet: The Exhilarating Experience of Working with Rick Smalley," Dr. Robert F. Curl, '54, University Professor Emeritus, Duncan Hall, Rice University (2 DVDs), February 23, 2007 (Box 12)
  - A Brief History of Carbon, Robert Curl at the NASA Rice Nucleation and Growth Workshop III, Canyon of the Eagles Lodge (2 DVDs), April 15, 2007 (Box 12)
  - Richard E. Smalley Institute/Energy and Environmental Systems Institute Joint Seminar/Tutorial - Nano Down Hole: A New Funding Opportunity for 2008, Dr. George Hirasaki, Rice University Department of Chemical and Biomolecular Engineering, Duncan Hall (DVD), Nov 20, 2007 (Box 12)
  - CNST Archive 96: 101 Presentations in the Physics Main Hall (DVD), n.d. (Box 12)
  - CNST Archive 96: DVD 1, n.d. (Box 12)
    Scientific footage of an experiment sent to a colleague, n.d.; B-roll footage of microscope views from the cutting of the Nanorope that led to the explosion, n.d.; Computer Graphics, n.d.
  - CNST Archive 96: scientific footage. Comment reads: Air and H2 environments (few Torr) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - CNST Archive: DVD 1, n.d. (Box 12)
    Amazing Science (The Learning Channel) with a section on Nanotechnology, October 6, 1998; Richard Smalley - Rehearsal for a presentation, May 21, 1995
  - CNST Archive: DVD 2, n.d. (Box 12)
    Otto Koehler, IWF distribution, 1939; Nederland Omroeproduktie Bedrijf nv, Sptember 29, 1998; BBC Documentary on the Discovery of Fullerenes, n.d.
  - CNST Archive: DVD 3, n.d. (Box 12)
    CNST Groundbreaking, Computer/TEM Views: SWNT Ropes, n.d.; Sequence for Phys. Rev. Letter 76, 2511 NCSU Physics Department, 1996; America's Investment in the Future, March 2001; Nanotopia - BBC/Learning Channel, October 31, 1995
  - CNST Archive: DVD 4, n.d. (Box 12)
    Nobel Prize Winners, December 19, 1996; Chemistry Award, December 8, 1996; Smalley and Curl Awarded Nobel Prize, October 9-19, 1996; Welch Award, October 1992; Nanotube Fluorescence, August 2, 2002; White Nanotube, n.d.; Black Nanotube, n.d.; Destroyer Grid, n.d.; Destroyer Dime, n.d.; Repeating Sequence to Accompany Phys Rev Lett 76 2511, 1996
  - CNST Archive: METS 2000 Engineer's Club, Dr. Richard Smalley, Guest Speaker (DVD), n.d. (Box 12)
  - CNST Archive - Nanospace: Presentation/Documentary on the Concept of Nanospace, Nanoscience, and Nanotechnology (DVD) (Box 12)
  - CNST Archive: Nobel Prize Clip and Rotating Bucky Ball Animation (DVD) (Box 12)
  - CNST Archive: Teleconference with Dr. Smalley and Others (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Rice University on Film Volume 2 DVD 1, n.d. (Box 12)
    Rice Today, 1977; Rice: Leading the New Century, 2003; 25th Anniversary of the School of Social Sciences, 2004; Small is Big at Rice: The World's Largest Nanotube Model, 2005; John Boles Lecture: Lovett to Leebron, 2005
  - AFM zip drives (26), 1998-1999 (Box 13, Case 1)
  - Office CD's (64) and DVD's (27), 2000-2010 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Conference Defining the Future May 31 - June 02, 2004 Manama, Kingdom of Bahrain (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Energy & Nanotechnology Workshop II Prospects for Solar Energy in the 21st Century #1, 2000 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Energy & Nanotechnology Workshop II Prospects for Solar Energy in the 21st Century #2, 2000 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Energy & Nanotechnology Workshop II Prospects for Solar Energy in the 21st Century #3, 2000 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Energy & Nanotechnology Workshop II Prospects for Solar Energy in the 21st Century #7, 2000 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Smalley Files, Presentations, Memorial Service, Interviews, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - "Nobelity: A Film by Turk Pipkin", 2005 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - World's Largest Nanotube Model April 22, 2005 Digital Photographs (Box 13, Case 2)
    - NASA Review 200507 CNL (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Direct Spinning of Carbon Nanotube Fibres - Alan Windle Feb 2005 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - SIUC Lecture & Reception 4-03-05, 2005 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - GMW05 Presentations 4/26/05, 2005 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - T.A.M.E.S.T. Annual Conference Presentation, Richard Smalley & Jack Kilby Memorial, 2006 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - LM Course 2006 (Box 13, Case 2)